Bush, E. Ogden; Papers apap233
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legislative Bills, 1959-1965; Undated; 2; 1.8 cubic ft.
  - Introduced February 16, 1965, S. INT. 1226 PRT. 1234, 1964 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 26)
  - Introduced February 17, 1965, S. INT. 1406 PRT. 1420, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 27)
  - Introduced February 18, 1965, S. INT. 1481 PRT. 1495, Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 28)
  - Introduced February 24, 1965, S. INT. 1741 PRT. 1769, Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 29)
  - Introduced February 24, 1965, S. INT. 1742 PRT. 1770, Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 30)
  - Introduced February 24, 1965, S. INT. 1743 PRT. 1771 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 31)
  - Introduced February 24, 1965, S. INT. 1744 PRT. 1772 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 32)
  - Introduced February 24, 1965, S. INT. 1745 PRT. 1773 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 33)
  - Introduced February 24, 1965, S. INT. 1820 PRT. 1848 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 34)
  - Introduced February 25, 1965, S. INT. 1891 PRT. 1924 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 35)
  - Introduced March 2, 1965, S. INT. 2115 PRT. 2164 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 36)
  - Introduced March 2, 1965, S. INT. 2116 PRT. 2165 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 37)
  - Introduced March 4, 1965, S. INT. 2393 PRT. 2480, Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 38)
  - Introduced March 4, 1965, S. INT. 2394 PRT. 2481, Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 39)
  - Introduced March 4, 1965, S. INT. 2424 PRT. 2511, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 40)
  - Introduced March 9, 1965, S. INT. 2552 PRT. 2671, Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 41)
  - Introduced March 10, 1965, S. INT. 2885 PRT. 3041 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 42)
  - Introduced March 10, 1965, S. INT. 2886 PRT. 3042 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 43)
  - Introduced March 10, 1965, S. INT. 2887 PRT. 3043 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 44)
  - Introduced March 10, 1965, S. INT. 2888 PRT. 3044, Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 45)
  - Introduced March 17, 1965, S. INT. 3143 PRT. 3350, Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 46)
  - Introduced March 17, 1965, S. INT. 3144 PRT. 3351, Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 47)
  - Introduced March 17, 1965, S. INT. 3145 PRT. 3352, Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 48)
  - Introduced March 17, 1965, S. INT. 3146 PRT. 3353, Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 49)
  - Introduced March 17, 1965, S. INT. 3334 PRT. 3572, Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 50)
  - Introduced March 22, 1965, S. INT. 3356 PRT. 3627 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 51)
  - Introduced March 23, 1965, S. INT. 3513 PRT. 3803, Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 52)
  - Introduced March 23, 1965, S. INT. 3514 PRT. 3804, Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 53)
  - Introduced March 23, 1965, S. INT. 3518 PRT. 3808 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 54)
  - Introduced March 29, 1965, S. INT. 3764 PRT. 4101 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 55)
  - Introduced March 29, 1965, S. INT. 3772 PRT. 4109 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 56)
  - Introduced March 31, 1965, S. INT. 3908 PRT. 4300 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 57)
  - Introduced March 31, 1965, S. INT. 3909 PRT. 4301 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 58)
  - Introduced April 5, 1965, S. INT. 3968 PRT. 4409, Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 59)
  - Introduced April 5, 1965, S. INT. 3969 PRT. 4410, Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 60)
  - Introduced April 5, 1965, S. INT. 3970 PRT. 4111 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 61)
  - Introduced April 5, 1965, S. INT. 3971 PRT. 4412 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 62)
  - Introduced April 5, 1965, S. INT. 3987 PRT. 4461 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 63)
  - Introduced May 17, 1965, S. INT. 4527 PRT. 5509 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 64)
  - Introduced June 15, 1965, S. INT. 4719 PRT. 5946 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 65)
  - Introduced February 19, 1963, A. INT. 4555 PRT. 4741 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 66)
  - Introduced February 27, 1963, A. INT. 4820 PRT. 5094, Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 67)
  - Introduced March 25, 1963, A. INT. 5094 PRT. 5793, Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 68)
  - Introduced March 25, 1963, A. INT. 5095 PRT. 5794, Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 69)
  - Introduced February 10, 1965, A. INT. 1994 PRT. 1994, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 70)